Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Labor Organizing and Trade, 1987-2013; Series 1
  - NAFTA & Mexico, 1988-2013; Series 1 Subseries 3
    - Protection Contract-Mexico, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Public Report of Review of Office of Trade and Labor Affairs Submission 2005-03, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Enlace's 10th Anniversary convention, March 7-9, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Mexican Government, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Lessons from NAFTA, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - The State of Labor Rights in Mexico, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Comit Fronterizo de Obreras, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Cananea Strike, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - IMF Strategic Meeting, Mexico City, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - NAFTA Fact Sheet, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - CAT, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - IMF-Labor Law, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Latin American Working Group-Mexico and Border Program, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - NAFTA Complaint-SME, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Solidarity Center/Days of Action, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Wiki Leaks, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Labor Law reform articles, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Mexican Labor News & Analysis Vol.17, No.2, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Tri-National Solidarity Alliance (TNSA) Draft Work Plan, 2012-2013; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - CAFTA & Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1987-2011; Series 1 Subseries 4
    This series houses research notes and correspondence of Steve Coats and other USLEAP staffers on labor strikes, union organizing campaigns, and commodity-based trade data for Central America and the Caribbean. The bulk of materials consists of printed email correspondence and attached news articles; other materials include assorted document drafts, handwritten notes, conference handouts/mailings, and newspaper clippings on disputes on labor organizing and trade policy, both related and unrelated to the Central American Free Trade Act as well as the Caribbean Basin Initiative.
    For materials focusing mainly on El Salvador, Honduras, or Nicaragua, see Series 1, Subseries 1.
    - Solidarismo Movement articles, 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Solidarismo-Costa Rica, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Solidarismo, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Caribbean Basin Free Trade Agreement packet, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - CBI proposal, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative-Crane Bill, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative program, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Caribbeann Basin Trade Security Act-Senator Bob Graham, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Citizen Trade Campaign-Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - House and Senate Targets for Caribbean Basin Trade Security Act, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Senate-Caribbean Basin Trade Security Act, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - CBI Parity Bill, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Dominican Republic Conference, 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Free Trade Area of the Americas (FTAA), 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Summit of the Americas, Santiago Chile [1/2], 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Summit of the Americas, Santiago Chile [2/2], 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Central American Newsletter drafts, 1999-2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO report-Caribbean Basin Trade Partnership Act, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Nicaragua-Caribbean Basin Initiative petition, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO Report-Andean Trade Promotion and Drug Eradication Act, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Costa Rica GSP, 2001-2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - CAFTA-Central America Free Trade Agreement, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Oversight Group, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Costa Rica targeting, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - ILRF Central America Project, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - ILO Costa Rica trips, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - IMOP Report, Costa Rica [1/2], 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - IMOP Report, Costa Rica [2/2], 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - CAFTA: AFLO-CIO, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - CAFTA articles, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - CAFTA-"Dear colleagues", 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - CAFTA-Human Rights Watch, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - CAFTA-ILO Report, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - CAFTA-Latin America Working Group, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - CAFTA statements, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - CAFTA Statement of Principles, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - CAFTA/USTR, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - CBTPA, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Development Alternatives, Incorporated (DAI) Guatemala, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Sandra Polaski article and correspondence-CAFTA, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - USTR-Dominican Republic, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - CAFTA Facts, Real Results, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Gilberto Soto murder, El Salvador, 2004-2009; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - GSP Press, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Guatemala GSP Petition, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Guatemala GSP Country Practices Review, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Human Rights Watch, June 2006 Vol. 16 No. 2 -"Turning a Blind Eye: Hazardous Child Labor in El Salvador, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Impact of NAFTA and Lessons for Future, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - MFA articles, 2004-2006; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - USTR and WOLA, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - CAFTA, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - CAFTA-Apparel, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - CAFTA-Guatemala Protests and Violence, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - CAFTA in the News, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Global Justice Committee-Agendas and Minutes [1/2], 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Global Justice Committee-CAFTA [2/2], 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Guatemala-Ambassador Allegeier, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - A Union Activists's Guide to CAFTA, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Guatemala Worker Rights Report drafts, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Central America trip, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - FESTRAS/SITINCA, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Guatemala CAFTA complaint, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Guatemala CAFTA, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Guatemala Government, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Guatemala-SITRABI, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Guatemala Violence/CAFTA, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Panama and El Salvador Violence, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Sitra Peten, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - UDEFEGUA-Unidad de Proteccion a Defensoras y Defensoras de Derechos Humanos de Guatemala, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Worker Rights Under the New Guatemalan Goverment: A Preliminary Report, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - CAFTAa-Labor Protections and the Dominican Republic, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Religious Leadership Network on Latin America -Annual Luncheon Program, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Costa Rica CAFTA Complaint, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Labor Standards and Compliance, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Homero Fuentes, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - MSICG, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - CAFTA-CSR, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Fontheim, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Colombia, 1997-2011; Series 1 Subseries 5
    This series houses research notes and correspondence of Steve Coats and other USLEAP staffers on labor strikes, union organizing campaigns, and commodity-based trade data for Central America and the Caribbean. The bulk of materials consists of printed email correspondence and attached news articles; other materials include assorted document drafts, handwritten notes, conference handouts/mailings, and newspaper clippings on disputes on labor organizing and trade policy both related and unrelated to Plan Colombia as well as the U.S.-Colombia Free Trade act.
    For materials focusing on other South American countries, or focusing on the Andean Free Trade Act, see Series 1, Subseries 3-"AFTA-Ecuador, Peru, and Bolivia."
    - Colombia:Proposed Conference Themes, undated; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Colombia SEIU Resolution, undated; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - VACTUB Renewal forms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Colombia Support Network, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Colombia bulletins, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Coco-Cola research, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Colombia/AFL-CIO, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Colombia/ATPA bill, 2000-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Colombia delegation trip, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-Escuela Nacional Sindical, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Colombia human rights groups, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Colombia Human Rights report, 2000-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Colombia-religious statements, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Colombia website information, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Human Rights in Colombia workshop, De Paul University, 2000; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Coca-Cola Campaign materials, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Coca-Cola Campaign, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Coca-Cola corporate standards, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Coca-Cola emails, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - CokeWatch Coalition, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Cervanto Lerma Guevara, homicide victim, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Colombia forums, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Colombia/IUF/Coca-Cola, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Colombia-SINALTRAINAL/Coca-Cola, 2001-2006; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Cristbal Uribe Beltran, homicide victim, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Colombia-Background information, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Colombia conference, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Colombia-Congress/Washington D.C., 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Colombia-ILO, 2001-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Colombia labor contacts, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Colombia labor rights advocacy, 2001-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Colombia Mobilization, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Colombia Monthly Trade Union Violence Report draft, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Colombia-National Labor Committee report, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Colombia/Senator Durbin, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Colombia Senator Durbin letter, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Colombia tour, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Colombia Trade Union Tour, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Colombia violence-Central Unitaria de Trabajadores (CUT), 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-Witness for Peace labor delegation, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - CCJC/Coca-Cola, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Delegation to Colombia, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - DYNCORP complaint, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Rhett Doumitt, 2001-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - US Congress/Colombia, 2001-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - USLEAP Letters to Coca-Cola, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - VACTUB ISSUE #1 mailing, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Violence Against Colombia Workers: An Advocacy Kit on U.S. Aid, 2001-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Coca-Cola/Panamco, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Coca-Cola shareholders meeting, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Colombia/Campaign for LAbor Rights/Coca-Cola, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Colombia-Coca-Cola, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Colombia-Coca Cola meeting, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Colombia and Coca Cola-Princeton report, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Colombia-Congress/Lane Evans, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Colombia-Congress, Swing Votes, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Colombia delegation, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Colombian Embassy, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Colombia-Impunity Campaign, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Colombia/International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Coca-Cola, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Colombia ILR Fund/Coca-Cola, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Colombia Labor Caucus, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Colombia protection program, 2002-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Colombia-Senator Durbin, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Colombia Union Resolutions, 2002-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-Wellstone, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Felipe Santiago Mendoza Navarro, homicide victim, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - ILRF Customs Complaint-cocoa, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Public Services International Mission to Colombia report, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Violence Against Colombian Workers: An Advocacy Kit on U.S. Aid, 2002-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions May 2002, Alert #1, Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions Bulletin, February 2002, Issue #2, Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions Bulletin, April 2002, Issue #3, Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions Bulletin Special Report, August 2002, Issue #4, Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions Bulletin, October 2002, Issue #5, Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unions Bulletin, Issue #6, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - VACTUB Survey, 2002-2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Coca-Cola Campaign, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Colombia/National Education Association, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Colombia Advocacy Materials, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Colombia-Anne Patterson-Correspondence, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Colombia-Brian Finnegan-Correspondence, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Colomba-Coca Cola/SINALTRAINAL, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Colombia-Congress-Voting Correspondence, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Colombia delegation materials, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Colombia delegation agenda and budget, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Colombia delegation participants, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Colombia/Global Exchange, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Colombia/ICTUR, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Colombia legislation, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Colombia, President Uribe Statement, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Colombia risks and arrests, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Colombia-U.S. Trade Union letter, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - IUF Coca Cola meeting, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Latin America Working Group letters, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Luis Cardona tour, Chicago-Coca Cola, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - SINTRAEMCALI, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - US Office on Colombia, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - VACTUB Issue #7 fax updates, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unionists Bulletin Issue #7, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Violence Against Colombian Trade Unionists Bulletin Issue #8, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - VACTUB donor reports and renewals, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - VACTUB mailing, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - AFTA notes, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Andean Free Trade Agreement testimony, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Andean Free Trade Agreement-talking points (1), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Washington Office on Latin America-Andean Free Trade Agreement (2), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Andean Free Trade Agreement (3), 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Colombia-Andean Free Trade Agreement, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Alliance for Responsible Trade-Andean Free Trade Agreement, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - "Assassination Is an Issue in Trade Talks" by Juan Forero, New York Times, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Oversize 136, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta press-negotiations, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - chapter notes-Impunity, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Colombia-Advocacy Kit, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Colombia-Andean Free Trade Agreement, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Colombia-Andean Free Trade Agreement, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Colombia-Coca Cola, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Colombia-Coca Cola, Worker Rights Consortium, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Colombia-"Dear Colleagues" letters, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Colombia/Ecuador delegation, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Colombia Delegation-budget, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Colombia-Drummond (1), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Colombia-Drummond (2), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Colombia Human Rights Certification, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Colombia-Human Rights Watch, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Colombia press, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Colombia report to ENS and CUT, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Colombia Report by US State, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Colombia reports/updates, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Colombian response-Free Trade Agreement, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Colombia Resolution, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Colombia Resolution, AFT National Convention, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Colombia-Santos and Sweeney, 2004-2006; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Colombia-Union letter to Senate, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Colombia-U.S. Senate, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Colombia Worker Rights [1/2], 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Colombia Worker Rights [2/2], 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Escuela Nacional Sindical report [1], 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Escuela Nacional Sindical-Colombia Union Worker Assasinations [2], 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Escuela Nacional Sindical-Colombia report [3], 2008; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Escuela Nacional Sindical-Colombia reports [4], 2010; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Jhony Menses asylum-Colombia, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Midwest Regional Joint Board conference, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - National Trade Strategy conference, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Human Rights/Farr-Schakowsky-McGovern Amendment, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - UNITE presentation on Colombia, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - US Trade Unions opposing more US Aid to Colombian military, 2004-2006; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Colombia-AFL delegation, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Colombia-Antonio Durango letters, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Colombia-Coca Cola, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Colombia-Congress advocacy, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Colombia-contact lists, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Colombia delegation, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Colombia-human rights meeting, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Colombia Impunity cases, 2005-2007; Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 93, Folder 20)